ANGELO GONZALEZ

(312) 307-6448 angelogonzalez@outlook.com

AWARDS

National Hispanic Scholar

ASSOCIATIONS

ACM Alianza IEEE Sigma Phi Epsilon

LANGUAGES

English Spanish

PROFILE

Computer scientist with 20+ years of experience developing 5,000+ web-based solutions for 80+ clients, including notable brands such as Domino's Pizza, Rolex, Firestone, Hyatt Hotels, Microsoft, UnitedHealth Group, Discover Card, Case/New Holland, WellPoint, AT&T, Northwestern University, IBM and more.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Consultant, Hyatt; Chicago, IL — 2017-2024

Initially leveraged Adobe Experience Manager and a SpringBoot API layer to develop over 1,600 AngularJS sites. These sites were then migrated into React and React Native components, built on NextJS which utilized GraphQL and are delivered to the edge through Akamai.

Senior Developer, United Healthcare; Chicago, IL — 2020-2024

Storybook-driven rewrite of an AngularJS Jenkins-based build pipeline, transforming NPM packages into React/React Native components which are scaffolded into a custom single-context React SPA, Android app, and iOS app using a GitHub Actions pipeline.

Senior Consultant, Microsoft; Chicago, IL — 2020-2021

For microsoft.com store (Adobe Experience Manager):

- Configured AEM Sling Dynamic Includes
- Implemented "Buy Box" React component into PDP AEM template
- Developed "Remote game installation to Xbox" React component
- · Conducted Gatling load testing
- · Performed Selenium automated testing

Senior Consultant, Valtech; Chicago, IL — 2016-2017

- Lead frontend developer for Adobe Experience Manager (AEM)-based meetings and events site for Hyatt (meetings.hyatt.com).
- Lead frontend developer for Groovy-based service quote submission site for Rolex.
- Lead frontend developer for AEM-based Digital Assets Management (DAM) repository file upload tool for Lundbeck.

EDUCATION

Northwestern University, Chicago, IL - M.S. CIS, 2017 Northwestern University, Chicago, IL - B.S. Computer Science, 2003

SKILLS

Typescript, React, React Native, Javascript, HTML5, CSS3, AEM, Webpack, NodeJS, Magento, Perl, Python, Java, C#, C/C++, Shell Scripting, Unix, VIM